{"success": 1, "total": 2100, "result": [{"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ff6", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "20,40,60", "optionC": "10,20,30", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": " ", "optionB": "10,30,50", "type": "1", "optionA": "10,30,60", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u4e0b\u9762\u7a0b\u5e8f\u7684\u8f93\u51fa\u7ed3\u679c\u662f\uff1f\n#include<iostream.h>\nvoid main(){\n    int n[][3]={10,20,30,40,50,60};\n    int (*p)[3];\n    p=n;\n    cout<<p[0][0]<<\",\"<<*(p[0]+1)<<\",\"<<(*p)[2]<<endl;\n}", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ff7", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "a>0&&!(b>0)", "optionC": "(a<=0)||(a%b>0)", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": " ", "optionB": "(a>b)&&(b>0&&a>0)", "type": "1", "optionA": "(b>=0)&&(a<=b?A+b:a-b)>0", "knowledge": "C#", "question": "\u8bbe\u6709C#\u8bed\u53e5\uff1aint a=5,b=4; \n\u5219\u4e0b\u5217\u8868\u793a\u6761\u4ef6\u7684\u8868\u8fbe\u5f0f\u4e2d\u503c\u4e3a\u201c\u5047\u201d\u7684\u662f()", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ff8", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "ls -d.txt", "optionC": "find . \".txt\"", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": " ", "optionB": "ls *.txt", "type": "1", "optionA": "find . -name \"*.txt\"", "knowledge": "Linux", "question": "\u5982\u679c\u4f60\u60f3\u5217\u51fa\u5f53\u524d\u76ee\u5f55\u4ee5\u53ca\u5b50\u76ee\u5f55\u4e0b\u6240\u6709\u6269\u5c55\u540d\u4e3a\u201c.txt\u201d\u7684\u6587\u4ef6\uff0c\u90a3\u4e48\u4f60\u53ef\u4ee5\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u547d\u4ee4\u662f", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ff9", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "<%String myBean=(String)pageContext.getAttribute(\"stringBean\",PageContext.PAGE_SCOPE);%>", "optionC": "<bean:write name=\"stringBean\"/>", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": " ", "optionB": "<%=stringBean%>", "type": "1", "optionA": "<bean:write name=\"helloWorld\"/>", "knowledge": "PHP", "question": "\u4ee5\u4e0bJSP\u4ee3\u7801\u5b9a\u4e49\u4e86\u4e00\u4e2a\u53d8\u91cf\uff0c\u5982\u4f55\u8f93\u51fa\u8fd9\u4e2a\u53d8\u91cf\u7684\u503c\uff1f\n<bean:define id=\"stringBean\" value=\"helloWorld\"/>", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ffa", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "34", "optionC": "35", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": " ", "optionB": "4", "type": "1", "optionA": "3", "knowledge": "PHP", "question": "\u5047\u5b9a\u6240\u6709\u53d8\u91cf\u5747\u5df2\u6b63\u786e\u5b9a\u4e49\uff0c\u5219\u4e0b\u5217\u7a0b\u5e8f\u6bb5\u8fd0\u884c\u540ex\u7684\u503c\u662f\uff08\uff09 \na=b=c=0;x=35;\nif(!a) x--;\nelse if(b);\nif(c) x=3;\nelse x=4;", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ffb", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u5faa\u73af\u6362\u884c\u6253\u5370\u5168\u90e8\u8bb0\u5f55", "optionC": "\u65e0\u4efb\u4f55\u7ed3\u679c", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": " ", "optionB": "\u62a5\u9519", "type": "1", "optionA": "\u53ea\u6253\u5370\u7b2c\u4e00\u6761\u8bb0\u5f55", "knowledge": "PHP", "question": "\u4ee5\u4e0b\u4ee3\u7801\u6267\u884c\u7684\u7ed3\u679c\u662f()  \n<?php \n    mysql_connect(\"localhost\",\"root\",\"\")\n    $result=mysql_query(\"select id,namefrom tb1\");\n    while($row=mysql_fetch_array($result,MYSQL_ASSOC))\n    {echo\"ID;\",$row[0],\"Name;\",$row[];}\n?>", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ffc", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "5", "optionC": "3", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": " ", "optionB": "9", "type": "1", "optionA": "7", "knowledge": "PHP", "question": "\u8fd0\u884c\u4e0b\u9762\u7a0b\u5e8f\u6bb5\uff0c\u8f93\u51fa\u7ed3\u679c\u4e3a() \n<?php\n    $arr = array(3,5,7,9,6);\n    echo $arr[3];\n?>", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ffd", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "4\u548c20", "optionC": "5\u548c4", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": " ", "optionB": "3\u548c15", "type": "1", "optionA": "20\u548c5", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u5047\u5b9a\u4e00\u4e2a\u7c7b\u7684\u6784\u9020\u51fd\u6570\u4e3aA(int aa,int bb){a=aa--;b=a*bb;}\uff0c\u5219\u6267\u884cA x(4,5);\u8bed\u53e5\u540e\uff0cx.a\u548cx.b\u7684\u503c\u5206\u522b\u4e3a\uff08\uff09", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26ffe", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "unmount /mnt/cdrom /dev/hdc", "optionC": "umount /dev/hdc", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": " ", "optionB": "unmount /dev/hdc", "type": "1", "optionA": "umount /mnt/cdrom /dev/hdc", "knowledge": "Linux", "question": "\u5c06\u5149\u76d8/dev/hdc\u5378\u8f7d\u7684\u547d\u4ee4\u662f?", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf26fff", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u5f53\u521b\u5efa\u4e00\u4e2a\u65b0\u7ebf\u7a0b\u65f6", "optionC": "\u5f53\u8be5\u7ebf\u7a0b\u8c03\u7528sleep()\u65b9\u6cd5\u65f6", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": " ", "optionB": "\u629b\u51fa\u4e00\u4e2a\u4f8b\u5916\u65f6", "type": "1", "optionA": "\u5f53\u4e00\u4e2a\u4f18\u5148\u7ea7\u9ad8\u7684\u7ebf\u7a0b\u8fdb\u5165\u5c31\u7eea\u72b6\u6001\u65f6", "knowledge": "Java", "question": "\u4e0b\u9762\u90a3\u4e9b\u60c5\u51b5\u53ef\u4ee5\u7ec8\u6b62\u5f53\u524d\u7ebf\u7a0b\u7684\u8fd0\u884c\uff1f", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}, {"ID": "55fa697ee4b043d0caf27000", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u4ece\u672c\u5730\u786c\u76d8\u9a71\u52a8\u5668\u8fdb\u884c\u5b89\u88c5", "optionC": "\u901a\u8fc7NFS\u8fdb\u884c\u7f51\u7edc\u5b89\u88c5", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": " ", "optionB": "\u901a\u8fc7Telnet\u8fdb\u884c\u7f51\u7edc\u5b89\u88c5", "type": "1", "optionA": "\u901a\u8fc7HTTP\u8fdb\u884c\u7f51\u7edc\u5b89\u88c5", "knowledge": "Linux", "question": "Redhat 9\u6240\u652f\u6301\u7684\u5b89\u88c5\u65b9\u5f0f\u4e0d\u5305\u62ec?", "title": "Baidu-2016\u7814\u53d1\u5de5\u7a0b\u5e08\u5728\u7ebf\u6a21\u62df\u7b14\u8bd5"}]}